import 'package:projectquiz/Screens/Quizz/InfoRmation%20Technology/Model/question.dart';

const List<Question> questions = [
  Question(
    question: '1. Information technology deals with',
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    options: [
      'a) Information',
      'b) Data',
      'c) Knowledge',
      'd) all',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '2. Factors of production include',
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    options: [
      'a) Source',
      'b) Cost and location',
      'c) Capital labour and material',
      'd) All are true',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '3. Economic trends include information relating to',
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    options: [
      'a) Consumers and employment',
      'b) Productivity, capital investment, etc.',
      'c) All are true',
      'd) None is true',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '4. The first calculating device is called',
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    options: [
      'a) Multiplying machine',
      'b) Analytical engine',
      'c) Adding machine',
      'd) ABACUS',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '5. binary value of 25 is',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      'a) 10101',
      'b) 11001',
      'c) 00111',
      'd) 11111',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question:
        '6. Diligence, accuracy, versatility, reliability, storage, speed, and time are',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: [
      'a) Characteristics of a computer',
      'b) Objectives',
      'c) Goals',
      'd) Strategies',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question:
        '7. Hardware cost, system analysis and operation costs reflect different types of',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: [
      'a) Cost of information',
      'b) Value of information',
      'c) Types of info',
      'd) All are true',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '8. Number system is',
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    options: [
      'a) Positional',
      'b)  Non-positional',
      'c) Positional and non-positional',
      'd) None of the above',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '9. If you want info on jeans, you could use the',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: [
      'a) VERONICA',
      'b) FTP',
      'c) BROWSER (Internet Explorer, Netscape)',
      'd) Dial-up access',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '3. Economic trends include information relating to',
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    options: [
      'a) Consumers and employment',
      'b) Productivity, capital investment, etc.',
      'c) All are true',
      'd) None is true',
    ],
  ),
];
